[Music]
hello everyone this is marianski again
and welcome to my youtube channel i'm
here again guys
and so my today's vlog or my video for
today
i am a
[Music]
once a month innovating
new skin
[Music]
so i will try again another set
non-renovating rejuvenating
set so um before
[Music]
rejuvenating set so you can uh
check it out also but today
maybe
[Music]
this is one of her um
what do you call this one best seller
i know product so supporting
so for me i'm using registration
or dead skin what i mean is dead skin
not dry skin dry skin and dead skin is
very awesome
i think so i am so i'll try this
uh product and so there the
this product has a soap
um so my
my toner and the
myron bleaching cream or rejuvenating a
cream
and there is a sunblock cream spf
45 and there is a toner also and then
the whole chick soap so
we're gonna open this yeah we're gonna
open this
package now beauty
vault glass skin essential
so maybe yeah and learn some of the
girls
but the thing glass skin essentials
[Music]
we try the glass skin
glass skin essentials again so the
premium rejuvenating sets
reality vault so if you
i will finish this maybe
just for exfoliation after the
peeling peeling effect uh maybe after
three days or four days or five days
um
[Music]
and then i will just finish this set and
then
papa papa rescuing skin so
um after that moisturizers
sorry
after so what's inside this
box and uh the secret
is finally out again beauty vault glass
skin essential premium
rejuvenating set brings you and
all in one rejuvenating facial
set carefully formulated and tested to
help you achieve
that younger favor
and blemishes free skin you've
been dreaming
i and so step one use beauty
vaults premium clothing
um uh what you call this one
instructions
if you're always using kind of rich
innovating set menu
of course but
i will still read this one use beauty
vault
uh premium project soap as your regular
facial cleansing sole
apply to damp face and lather
it or in circular motion
for two to three minutes before rinsing
the water so you have to
uh when you call um circular motion just
like that
so so you have to
massage it for two to three minutes
before
it rinse so a
after that place a small amount of
beauty of all premium regenerating toner
on the cotton ball and apply likely to
face and neck
and upward motion of course
after nothing
is to uh pot
face towel but um to you in
water and then you're gonna uh
we use cotton balls or something like
this
cotton balls i cotton balls and para
[Music]
you know our skin i i i mean our face
is delicate so hello
the third one is apply liberal amount of
beauty volt
premium tented sunblock cream spf 45 30
minutes before
sun exposure we apply as needed
number three which is a sunblock
but for me naman
it so i'm using it
again and then use beautiful premier
project
some morning at night young night the
same routine
except some morning now you have to make
spf 45
now beauty vault
ayan song
[Music]
i still have this so pero calcium
chap not not kind not kind of this
so
in front of you so i used some uh
even classic soap but later on to
book us i will use this soap na that one
and then i'm gonna try this toner
yeah so anyways
[Music]
and then there is
there is this is number oh but
number three yeah number three
say the english innovating cream and
this is the sunblock
so the gabingayon i'm gonna use the
toner and then the cream
and tomorrow the same routine and then
the
the sunblock okay china
again one of my one of my reasons why i
am
using regenerating uh set
because i have some free calcium
if you can see and frequency and free
kills
and frequency so
orpikas yeah
ever since i got it before because i did
not care before
about my skin no on
beach and without putting any sunblock
something like that anyway
and so this is my first day using this
um product and
[Music]
um
up up up up up up
up up up next
we're gonna do we're gonna use this
regenerating cream i am not saying
[Music]
or something like that and then the
cream
hindi
[Music]
maybe because of uh first first lego but
we will see for second third for it
uh hang on
for sure and then uh for three or five
days may affect
people 15 days to 30 days
[Music]
effective products
i'll see you again after this phrase my
my effect wait so i'll see you again
as a product review
[Music]
so that's for today guys thank you thank
you for always
um watching me and ski and uh thank you
for not subscribing my answer please
subscribe
and uh have a nice day everyone
and god bless us all